intechgrity.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy policy - InTechgrity

Y our Privacy is important to us. We are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our site [http://www.inTechgrity.com](https://www.intechgrity.com/) . The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site….  

#### The Information We Collect

We use **statcounter** and **google analytics tools** to collect the information. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. Also our Blog is hosted on blogspot platform. So all the information collected by Blogger is not in any way controlled by us and you are requested to see Blogger Privacy Policy.

#### Cookies and Web Beacons

We also use third party advertisements on **inTechgrity** to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

 **DoubleClick DART cookies** The [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher’s website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user’s browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit on our sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

#### Commenting System

We have previously used **[intensedebate](http://intensedebate.com/)** commenting system as our default blog commenting system. Now we are using default WordPress commenting. The name and website URl are displayed on comments, but email address is secure with us. We do not share it with outside parties. While comments are welcome from anybody, we reserve the right to remove any comment that is not deemed suitable for publication. This could include but is not limited to objectional and abusive comments. Hate, racist comments, or any other form of prejudice will be removed and the poster will be banned! Comments made for sole purpose of getting backlinks or advertizing your/any product will not be accepted. Link to third party website will require moderation and we reserve the rights to edit/delete such links. Spam in any form will not be accepted and will be deleted immediately. We may take action against such spammers.

#### Newsletter

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter (powered by Feedburner), we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. To know more about Subscribing to Newsletter Please [Click here](https://www.intechgrity.com/subscribe-rss-feed/)

#### Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

#### Copy Limitations

Please don’t copy the whole post. A short paragraph with content in quotes is acceptable with a link-back to the post at **inTechgrity.com**

 **Credit the Source:** You need to clearly highlight the fact that the content was derived from [http://www.](https://www.intechgrity.com/)[inTechgrity](https://www.intechgrity.com/).com

 **Link Back:** You need to link back to the article from which you derived the excerpt.

#### Advertisers

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. Currently we work with a number of advertiser advertiser – **[Technorati Engage](https://beta.technoratimedia.com/privacy.cfm), [Infolinks](http://infolinks.com/privacy.html;jsessionid=20ACF59D29883CEB7A60AC561B706362), [Chitika](http://chitika.com/privacy_policy.php)** and **[Google Adsense](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html)**. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

###  _ **Why do I see double underlined links?**_

 _These links are part of an advertising service called Infolinks. Infolinks uses the In Text method of advertising: they take my text and create links within it. If you hover your mouse over these[double underline links](http://www.infolinks.com/), you will see a small dialog box containing advertisement related to the text marked. You can choose to either move the mouse away and go on with your browsing, or to press on the box and go to the ad which is relevant to our text. __To learn more about Double Underline Link Ads –[Click Here](http://www.infolinks.com/)._

#### Copyrights

Supreme caution has been taken to make sure that there are no copyright infringements in terms of the multimedia content and the subject matter that is posted in this blog. If you find anything that could be considered a violation of the copyright norms, please contact me immediately.

#### Contact Information

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please [Contact us](https://www.intechgrity.com/contct-us/ "greenTechspot Contact Us form").
